[
    {
        "question": "What is P.T. Usha's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Rawalpindi Express",
            "Payyoli Express",
            "Master Blaster",
            "Bengal Tiger"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Shoab Akhtar's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Flying Sikh",
            "Plastic Girl",
            "Rawalpindi Express",
            "Haryana Hurricane"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sachin Tendulkar's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Master Blaster",
            "Torpedo",
            "Water Queen",
            "Payyoli Express"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sourav Ganguly's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Haryana Hurricane",
            "Bengal Tiger",
            "Flying Sikh",
            "Rawalpindi Express"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Kapil Dev's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Master Blaster",
            "Bengal Tiger",
            "Haryana Hurricane",
            "Payyoli Express"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Bula Choudhury's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Plastic Girl",
            "Water Queen",
            "Torpedo",
            "Flying Sikh"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Nadia Comaneci's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Water Queen",
            "Torpedo",
            "Plastic Girl",
            "Rawalpindi Express"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ian Thorpe's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Torpedo",
            "Haryana Hurricane",
            "Bengal Tiger",
            "Master Blaster"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Milkha Singh's nickname?",
        "choices": [
            "Plastic Girl",
            "Payyoli Express",
            "Flying Sikh",
            "Water Queen"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the image, which sport is Michael Jordan associated with?",
        "choices": [
            "Boxing",
            "Swimming",
            "Basketball",
            "Athletics"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    }
]